<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Pasco County, Florida - ARES</title><link>https://pascoares.org/</link><description>Recent content on Pasco County, Florida - ARES</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://pascoares.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://pascoares.org/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pascoares.org/about/</guid><description>Who We Are We are the Amateur Radio Emergency Service (&amp;ldquo;ARES&amp;rdquo;) team in Pasco County, Florida. &amp;ldquo;ARES&amp;rdquo; is part of the &amp;ldquo;Amateur Radio Relay League&amp;rdquo; (&amp;ldquo;ARRL&amp;rdquo;). Organizationally, we are part of the &amp;ldquo;West Central Florida&amp;rdquo; Section of the ARRL. Pasco County is on the Central Gulf Coast of Florida, North of Tampa Bay. &amp;ldquo;Providing Pasco County, FL with Effective Emergency Communication!&amp;rdquo;
Leadership Team Within the ARES organization, Pasco ARES has a team of amateur radio operators who serve as the leadership group.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://pascoares.org/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pascoares.org/contact/</guid><description>For more information about Pasco County, FL ARES or to join, please email us at n7cgc@arrl.net</description></item><item><title>Events</title><link>https://pascoares.org/events/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pascoares.org/events/</guid><description> Date Time Event Type Location TBD TBD TBD TBD</description></item><item><title>Mission</title><link>https://pascoares.org/mission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pascoares.org/mission/</guid><description>Amateur Radio has a long and honored tradition of providing communications during times of emergency. This is in keeping with the first of the stated purposes of the Amateur Radio Service found in the FCC rules:
97.1(a) Recognition and enhancement of the value of the amateur service to the public as a voluntary noncommercial communications service, particularly with respect to providing emergency service.
The primary mission of Pasco County Amateur Radio Emergency Service is to provide dedicated volunteer federally licensed amateur radio operators to government, non-governmental and community agencies during times of emergency and disasters thereby increasing safety for and expediting the recovery process of the affected agencies and communities.</description></item><item><title>Nets</title><link>https://pascoares.org/nets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://pascoares.org/nets/</guid><description>The Pasco County Amateur Radio Emergency Service On-Air Nets
Pasco ARES / SKYWARN Weekly Net
The Pasco County ARES/SKYWARN Net meets on-the-air each Wednesday night at 7:30 PM local time. Currently we are linking up to four Pasco County repeaters via echolink. You can connect to anyone of the repeaters listed below. The primary repeater is 146.670.
Repeater Call Sign Location Frequency/Tone Echo Link Node All Star Node GCARC WA4GDN New Port Richey 146.</description></item></channel></rss>